咧就誒，兩點半誒個時間到，亦都夠法定人數。
噉我哋呢條咧叫《二零一四年海外律師豁護認許資格修訂規則生效日期公告》小組委員會咧，噉我哋咧就已經開會議，第一次咧我哋選呢個主席有冇提名？
石禮謙議員，Dennis Kong。
啊，Dennis Cole，OK，啊，郭議員有冇人和議？
係啦，咪分議員和議。O K，噉啊，因為睇嚟都冇第二個可以提名到和議，咁所以咧，我接受啊主席，主啊，你接受就得㗎啦。啊，噉啊，噉我宣佈咧，就係啊郭議員咧當選主席。
上市。
hello。
好，噉我哋誒有請，我諗唔使選副主席啦嚇，噉就我哋。
嚇！呢個會咧，我哋係得一個鐘頭嘅啫。誒，我亦都要三點半都要離開。咁誒，或者我哋有請誒今日嘅官員係出席。
淨係律師會啫，好啊，噉我哋有請律師會嘅代表出席啊。
政府，但佢就。
得佢。
即係冇咩role to play，所以佢就。
OK。
我知道。
我記得喎，我記得，不過個view是nothing controversial。
畀佢即係多食下。
綜藝節目，我冇睇太多嘢。
just exam right.
佢啲exemption有冇得apply the exemption？
都可以。
幾時會可以？
ok。
Are they coming?
yes.
得閒。
可唔可以用英文啊？可唔可以用英文啊？
係。
Okay, well welcome everyone from the Law Society. I've been informed that there is no going to be no representatives from the Secretary for Justice today, but we'll soldier on nevertheless. We only have one hour today, so first of all, I'm going to invite representative of the Law Society.
To explain their position on this issue, and then we'll open the floor to the members. Thank you.
多謝主席。
好，my name's Dennis Brock. I chair the Foreign Lawyers Committee of the Law Society.
Before you, there are these amendments which are focused on. The only substantial amendment to our rules is to bring in a new
And yet, unnumbered head six, which would be the new constitutional exam.
As you know, any foreign lawyer wanted to be admitted in Hong Kong has to go through the overseas lawyer qualification exam, of which there are presently five heads.
There will be an additional head on our constitution.
There are then three.
或四項，的，釐清，，effectively codifying or memorialising what is already policy in relation to considering applications to sit the exam.
The amendments were passed by Ledgeco.
and the negative vetting period expired on the 28th of May this year.
The only residual aspect is the commencement date, which we have proposed as 2nd of January, 2015.
Thank you, Ms. Brock.
Any other representative for law society would like to contribute?
If no, then I'm gonna open up the.
Panel to the members of this committee，啊，議員有冇咩提問？
係。你而家做好又幾時會做好嗰個syllabus啊？嗰個成個package係嘛？即係嗰個誒誒時間表係嘛？啊嚇。
有清或者。
講講嗰個時間表嘅問題。
係。
既然佢講廣東話，不如我講啦。其實咧，誒，英文都得嘅，冇問題。
啊，OK。
In fact, the the only addition to the
exam is the paper on Hong Kong constitutional law, and all the other examination we have been holding it for.
How many years? 1995. Since 1995, so it's a 20 years practice. So there's only the only addition is a one additional paper, and I understand from the secretary of the law society.
that they have.
In that line, up the panel for that.
paper。
And invitation was sent out.
所以， we are pretty sure that the
will be ready for the commencement in the coming January.
Thank you.
If if there are no other questions, yes, Mr. James Towe.
主席，係，冇意思，因為因為我誒記得咧嗰陣時內會咧，我唔係我提出成立嘅。
就係阿湯家華議員咧，就我見佢舉手提出成立嘅。
噉就第一，我見佢就冇參加呢個委員會咧。我你有冇知唔知道佢有冇咩嘢係誒問？有佢同我講過，我會代佢提出問題。噉你不如你你問啦，因為因為我咧就即係驚唔夠人咧，就幫手組成個委員會，等佢可以問嘅。係噉，如果你如果係我係有問題嘅，噉我可以聽聽你啲問題噉樣啊噉樣。好，嗯，in fact the
嗯。
The questions that I have, since no other members have questions, is regarding the policy of overseas lawyers of the Law Society. The policy of the Law Society in granting exemptions in the past regarding papers, and also this new paper that which will be introduced.
What is the policy regarding possible exemptions, if any, if an applicant wishes to apply in the future?
And who will set the syllabus? And I understand the panel of examiners will. Is there? Is it possible to give us some sort of
indication or guidance on what sort of questions or what sort of topics will be examined under this this heading. So, couple questions: exemptions, policy on overseas lawyers generally, and also actual examination topics under this heading.
That's.
That's for me, I guess.
The gateway to being allowed to take the exam is.
兩年。如果如果申請人有五年經驗，然後他們有資格申請豁免。
Generally, if someone has at least at present, if they have five years, they are automatically exempted from Head Two, which is litigation. Effectively, Head One is conveyancing, and it is in in view of the fact that Hong Kong has.
A globally unique conveyancing system, based upon a riding of Yorkshire system in 1924. There is no possibility or prospect of anyone obtaining an exemption from conveyancing. So that's always sat. Head three is company commercial, which my friend John Chan looks after and makes sure.
The candidates have adequate company commercial experience. It used to be the case that if you're a commercial litigator, that was probably good enough. We're somewhat more stringent now in wanting to see a proper level of commercial law awareness. Head for is accounts and ethics. Essentially, if you've taken a course and been passed in something.
which looks like our sister accounts rules, then we're comfortable. So put it bluntly, if you come from England or Australia or New Zealand or Canada and have passed the accounts course, that's fine.
It's a combined paper with ethics, so the ethical standards are broadly similar. Some jurisdictions have bifurcated and don't have an accounts module, and that's been causing us some internal.
discussion.
And I think we're moving to a point where, unless your jurisdiction has an accounts module, you'll be required to take head four. The reason being is that the handling of client funds is very important, and an awareness of our sister's accounts rules is very important.
所以，那係廣義上嘅架構，係點樣去處理豁免嘅問題。
It's fair to say that we are, how one put it, John, inclusive. Yeah, if I may add something to what Dennis said.
what then is said is。
About epicentrum, a common law jurisdiction.
所以，那係五 years，那。
previous experience in the practice of law，such an applicant would be entitled for exemptions，but for lawyers from non-common law jurisdictions。
normally，the，we，we，don't，grant，exemption。
except。
嗯，The。
啲papers on on the principal common law.
which is an oral examination, if an applicant from law and common law jurisdiction, and he has set or passed a
Well，taking courses in common law，like masters in common law in the local university，then we will grant exemption to those non-common law jurisdiction lawyers。Otherwise。
no exemptions granted to any non-common-law jurisdiction lawyers.
And for sitting exam, these lawyer from non-criminal law jurisdiction, we require them to have five years' previous experience instead of two for the for the criminal law jurisdiction lawyers.
And that period of exemption or period of experience must be in the previous ten years. So if someone hasn't been practising, if they've been farming for the past ten years, then they are.
shut out.
所以， for someone who is from a non-common law jurisdiction but has taken something like the master of common law program at say the Hong Kong U, he or she would be regarded as a common law lawyer who would be, or still a non-common law lawyer, but who would be qualified for exemption after five years. No, if they if they apply
作為一名民事律師，但他們碰巧有修讀過學術課程，則我們會考慮該課程的內容，如果它滿足。
us that it matches the the requirements, the six core topics of a common law subject of a common law exam, then we'll exempt them from the vivre, which is head five.
One of these amendments is a sort of tidying up amendment, which is if.
We had a slight anomaly in years gone by, which is someone came from say.
typically the PRC qualified in the PRC and then went to New York and qualified in New York. We took a first a first touch route, which meant your PRC you have to be a civil lawyer. Now there are many PRC lawyers who take the bar and.
China go to New York, spend 20 years in New York, and then come to Hong Kong, and that was ludicrous. So we've now taken the view, as a matter of policy, and now as a matter of rule change, that they can elect.
所以，那P.R.C.律師或法國律師或。
Dutch lawyer, if they've got a common law qualification, they can then say that's my point of entry, and then they can seek exemptions under their common law qualification.
But what I think, John, we we don't give exemptions for academic.
common law success.
我see。
唔同，changes。
Apart from the additional paper of the constitutional law, the change this time is also that we give the applicant the choice to choose.
Their jurisdiction. If they they they are admitted in different jurisdictions.
所以。
In cases like if they're middle inPLC and then
They went to England or went to the U.S. and get a common law jurisdiction qualification, then they can choose.
Obviously, the
The concern of the Hong Kong legal profession, I like to say and put this on record, is that although we run a so-called open jurisdiction that we welcome and encourage the best lawyers from around the world to come and work here in Hong Kong, we also want to ensure that there are sufficient checks and
balances and also sufficient qualification criterias that will be applied to assess whether a person is qualified to be a Hong Kong lawyer or indeed qualified for any exemptions. So for this head, what is your your view on going forward? How about for this specific head?
Well, is there any established sort of guidance or policy that you guys are thinking about?
Well, obviously it's new and it's a paper that, in fact, I think was a creation of mine and.
Martin Rogers some ten years ago.
因為我們認為重要。
That.
律師 had a grasp of our constitution.
誒。
It hasn't been set yet, but it's obviously going to focus on the basic law, and one assumes it'll focus on the the cases we've had in the last 17 years where the courts have sought to interpret the basic law.
啊，梁議員，你啱啱入咗嚟，你會唔會有咩問題啊？誒，我要跟一跟先，唔好意思。好啊。嚇，你哋傾緊咩啊？
阿石生，阿石議員。Yes, I'm glad that someone's back here now. I don't have to keep you company.
My question actually is quite simple. Understand that the Law Society is consulting on a examination for local lawyers. That people who who who call who actually graduated without attending the PCL. I think that was.
was being discussed in this chamber last year. Now, there are a lot of frustrated law graduates.
who failed to gain admission to PCIL by the three institutions.
and those graduates then if they go overseas and get gain admission, having got their L.B. or J.D. whatever it is.
having been qualified for for in overseas, can they come back and seek
嗯，嗯，this。
as what you call this abstention from this four heads? Because since they have studied a lot in Hong Kong and they well versed with the constitution, do they still need that five years requirement?
the fact they're the fact they've studied law in Hong Kong.
makes them eligible to be admitted in, say, England or Australia, but they apply for the exemption from the OLQE as being either an English or Australian lawyer, where they took their first degree is not.
Of our concern, we look at their their place of qualification, and then they can seek exemption if they've gone through the gateways. But the but the the purpose of setting for the heads for constitutional law, convening and so they would have studied this in their undergraduate years.
所以， why did they need to sit for examination again?
without I mean without the five years because a lot of people we do need I like the openness of this profession and different from barristers there is a close shop but you you are actually opening the doors to attract more talents to Hong Kong which is a financial commercial centre of the world so we need a lot of lawyers and.
the the very nature of the control by the Trinity University to debar people from entering into the the lawyer's field, which is rather pathetic. So so basically, this is a way out for people who have actually studied locally and passed.
the examination having qualif need because they don't want to be qualified overseas because of this arcade system of this control by the three university badly so so they gain admissions overseas and coming back to they still my question is very simple they were worth of all the heads of the different examination.
Why they need to sit for that examination if they are if they have been less than five years experience?
Mr. Le Broc. Mr. Lee Chan, two point to clarify your your questions.
I still remember when before I joined the legal profession, I was in the transport department.
所以people， they can pass the exam here， the driving test， so they they went overseas and get a license and come back to Hong Kong and change for Hong Kong driving license。
所以，那係某啲你你，似乎，你係講緊，但係，有，有。
something different. One is that we recognise the people's
practice and law experience。
not the academic qualification. So, regardless of what they have studied.
The basic requirements is that if there are common common law's restriction, we need them to have practice.
The law of his own jurisdiction for at least two years before he is allowed to sit examination. Yeah, right. For a common law jurisdiction, five years. But the so the second point is, you talk about convening paper.
as far as I understand.
在香港，你只可以研究佢嘅發明，你係PCRL。
但係，如果你完成咗PCLL，你唔你唔 need to take the the overseas lawyers examination。
you can you can just go straight.
to Chinese Chinese ship in Hong Kong.
但係，但
Very likely. No, no, no one gets exempted from conveyancing. Okay. Regard because there's no, as I said, I think you may have missed it.
香港系統的傳承是獨特，它基於一個系統，在英格蘭約克郡的一個選區從一九二四年開始，他們放棄了它，然後我們有八十五年的香港普通法。沒有任何人來。我同意你，我沒有，我沒有在做辯論，我是在做。
case for the many, many and frustrated graduates who are forced overseas, unless until you have that examination.
as as proposed by the law society under consultation now that they can come back and sit for that examination, that they can be qualified and then enter into the system. But we are forcing out a lot of young people out from Hong Kong into overseas for for for for admissions. And I'm I'm
asking you to consider it.
作為一個特殊類別， of those people who want to make Hong Kong their home, who want to work in Hong Kong as a lawyer, and being deprived because of that three university, they they took a lot of money encouraging people to study law, but not by admission of qualification by.
By a mission of merit, a lot of local graduates were actually deprived of the chance to enter into the profession because they can't start the PCL. So I'm totally in support of law society to start a thinking now that which is under consultation on.
一 examination which I think is a very good thing for a lot of our young lawyers to be. You know, sorry, I'm just.
considered about this.
Specific case is very unique. We have churn out a lot of law graduates, but every year we limited the number of people into the profession. Not by the law society, but by the three universities, which is not the purpose of university.
我我完全同意，就是是，整個事情必須在律師公會的控制之下。對於律師，但係 somehow 這個事情係唔係噉樣。所以如果你可以考慮回顧，唔係針對呢個特別的條例，如果可以為呢個特殊羣體做啲嘢，幫助佢哋回歸香港。
那係一個情況，我認為係好重要。唔係關係呢個，但係趁呢個機會，唔係完全唔關係，係一個公平嘅問題。我認為，Mr. Brok。
Well, thank you for your comments. Good to know we've got another vote in favour of changing the system.
As you rightly point out, it's beyond the remit of.
the the foreign lawyers committee, although the relationship is that if if there were to be law society files introduced in Hong Kong, that would possibly eradicate the need for the overseas lawyers qualification exam because it would be a single point of entry. Thank you.
兩億。
嗯，Thank you, Chairman. In fact, I first of all I have to declare interest. I I I have been teaching at City University Law School, but I do not teach PCLL. So a long time back, I have suggested the legal community to explore the
possibility to have a common examination based on the fact that we truly have a number of good candidates who might not be able to go into PCCL. That is a fact. Okay, so for that, we I personally, and I know some other academics are are open. In fact, worthwhile to explore.
However, concerning whether examinations and this kind of additional conversion courses requirement is concerned, I truly think some of the courses are very unique for Hong Kong. I taught different kind of students from Europe, from other common laws, and also civil law.
system， so basic law， land law， are very different， and then concerning， actually you list some other more general course from from a point of view is contract law， tort， criminal etc.， we also have our own precedents now。
Because after handover, only Hong Kong precedents are binding to Hong Kong and other common law jurisdictions are persuasive. So I have a question to ask is concerning 5D.
5D，因為它有數據在。
啊！
That the period of privilege, privilege cannot be recognised as post-ambition experience. Do you mean that, in fact?
to be barrister overseas， you know， in many jurisdictions like Singapore， New Zealand， actually， they there is fusion。
The lawyers are both advocate and solicitor, right? So, how I I I would like to know. Maybe you can clarify. Does it mean that?
barrister pupilage is excluded as the eligibility eligibility criteria, or or just purely only the pupilage pupilage period. How about article collection?
I think you're talking about the description of how we define practice experience in the practice of law. So we've been counting article clerkship, traineeship, and legal practice course in lieu of training. So the two years they counted, they counted.
This two years article counted, but why not pupilage? Why? Because it's different. It's a different branch.
Because we are talking about practice experience in the practice of law for the purpose of overseas lawyers' qualification examination, which is targeted at solicitors. Okay, Chairman, may I further? Yes, please. In many jurisdictions, solicitors and barristers they now actually they have fusion. I'm I'm just concerned like.
Like, why you just exclude?
barrister or or pupillage, if they would like to take the same courses. In fact, I I graduated from Hong, I took PCCL in Hong Kong, so actually it's just a matter of choice after we finish PCCL to choose whether we will take pupillage or article clerkship. In some other jurisdictions, I know.
Actually， they don't have such distinction nowadays. So
Are you only referring to to to UK or what?
Yeah, if for jurisdictions that have fused profession, then there is no distinction, so we'll count the period of training. So if they have no distinction, then they will count that year of training.
That's right. Yes. Okay. So which jurisdiction is in your mind? UK? UK. Yes.
Right, many other common law jurisdictions are already no distinction between barrister and solicitor. Yes, UK is one.
any more.
因為你寫得 so explicitly。
Can't think of any. Can't think of any. Yeah, okay. But even you came. Singapore already come fusion. You you can be an advocate and a solicitor together.
所以。
also， in fact。
for this requirement of the duration of this, like for example, article clerkship. So you say common law jurisdiction, you only require two years. Non common law jurisdiction, which cover China and so for law countries.
then they need to have five years practising experience.
Does it include their? They might also have one or two year like training. Would it be counted also?
我哋max。
year，one year training only. Article clerkship also only count one year. I see.
Yes. Yes. I I thought it's only for the unless the one year or two years they are required for the admission into the foreign jurisdiction.
then we will count them. So, pupilage, for instance, if they are required as part of the admission requirement in that foreign jurisdiction.
要成為律師，然後我們會處理。我們會考慮。
但係，如果係一種喺，喺加上，到入境要求喺，喺
For instance, just give you example.
In U.S.
law school graduates after admission, they would typically get a clerkship, right, with the Supreme Court, with whatever court.
那會 not be counted.
In here, because that's not part of the practice, unless we construe it as good enough practice of law.
That's exactly what post admission, yes. Yes, Chairman.
no we.
嗱，
So will that will those people be counted? It's like they take the same lawyer's examination. Then later on they they will enter the judiciary. Will those years of experience be counted? Has it been as
Seriously considered the specific. Well, if if it's pre-admission, as Dennis reminded me, if a pre-admission, for instance, in New York, is not counted because it's not part of the admission requirement. Okay. But if it's post-admission in New York, we would consider it whether if it.
It is good enough practice of law as we as defined here, so its practice of law then will count it. But if it's not, then it's not counted. So may I clarify from you? If a graduate, a law graduate from UK.
They would like to go into the pupillage and then become a barrister.
如果他們 want to,
come back and choose this channel to become solicitor again.
Then， both privilege and their practice as a barrister will not be counted.
Am I correct?
No, the practice of barrister will be counted. Will be counted, so they can actually, it may be a switch miracle for those young barrister to come back to be soliciting in Hong Kong if they have proven experience. They have the sit exams.
Yeah, of course, you have to sit exam.
但係，佢哋 still need to take all those courses， right？
except the common law if they arrest them，嚇？Yes，sorry，I can't hear you。
except the paper and common law， the waiver， yeah。
Except the paper on common law, they are exempted. You mean, yeah? If the okay, the hypothetical English barrister, barrister from England and Wales, with five years experience.
會畀啊！
First of all, because he comes from England and Wales, he's exempted from.
The common law viva, so he then has at the moment four, and the next year we five exams, and if he goes through the various gateways of
五 years in the practice of law, he will be eligible at present to be exempt from procedure.
Typically, barristers don't get exempted from accounts and ethics because they don't do assisted accounts rules in England. Obviously, they have to do conveyancing. Commercial is
whether they can demonstrate adequate knowledge of commercial law.
We don't treat them any differently. The fact they come from the barristers' branch or the solicitors' branch in England, or wherever, is irrelevant. It's what
It's what they've been practising.
In their home jurisdiction, and indeed what they've been practising here. If they come here and register as a registered foreign lawyer, we give them credit.
哦，sorry， Chairman， I got some confusion. You just mentioned again five years practising experience, but from what we are aware of, we are mentioning graduate and also relevant common law experiences. Only two years, so exemptions is five. Exemptions is five. Gateway is two.
Okay. So embarrassed to coming from England.
has got to wait two years because in order to catch up with a solicitor from England who's done two years articles or what are they training contract, so the two kids who go to law school the same day in England, they can come to Hong Kong on broadly the same day and sit the exam.
嗯。
Okay. Now, if that child, if that person happens to be a Hong Kong graduate and went to England and spent ten years at Freshfields in London, then he can come back and get exempted and sit the OLQE and requalify in Hong Kong. We don't treat them any differently.
他可以 get the exemption of courses.
We, I mean, I think in a broad statement, we expect the foreign jurisdictions when they admit people in those common law jurisdictions to have satisfied themselves as to the academic component of the admission. We don't delve into what they studied at university.
係咪清？
多謝你。
And so all these required causes are taken care by the law society.
second。
they they all these additional all these required courses are taken care by the law society right so there are professional providers yeah I I read that so there will be a bundle of materials and they will have syllabus etc.
We have a set syllabus. It's we provide the syllabus. We don't provide courses, so we have commercial providers in the market to do that.
maybe maybe there is some confusion here I think.
啊！
We are dealing with foreign lawyers only, those lawyers who have been admitted overseas, not in Hong Kong. Okay, Hong Kongers can go through PCCL and they can automatically get into the legal profession. But then we are talking about these foreign lawyers who studied overseas and become a lawyers overseas.
They come to Hong Kong, they want to become Hongkongers. So we don't really offer them courses. We we decide whether they should sit all five exams, or they can sit just one. That's what we do. That's what the committee does.
and then in order to determine whether that person should.
Take five or take two, we look at their practice. If they had five years of practice of law, and that's very qualitative, in addition to quantitative, and then we use the syllabus to judge to certain extent whether that person has been exposed to these different areas of law.
as would a Hong Kong solicitor be required to be exposed to, over in the law school or in the PCLL?
或During the two years of training, so actually they can do self-studies.
just take the examination.
They can be taken online. They can study overseas if they wish. They don't need to be here to do it. They take the exam here, but they can study overseas.
In a way, we are trying to create a kind of a fair to certain extent, right? It's a fairness for for us treating foreign since we are inviting foreign lawyers to come to practice Hong Kong law, so we want to be kind to them and we want to set a standard. So that's basically the standard that's been.
set over the past many many years, unless you want to set a higher bar, that would be a different issue, right? Somebody another gentleman mentioned earlier.
I come from New York. I pass New York bar. I'm from China actually, but I pass New York bar.
The New York is different. Anybody has to take an exam, okay, 26 subjects at a time. So you have to go through the barbary or whatever review courses and then you take it. But then you must have one common law education, like one year. So you take a LLM, one year, then you are qualified. If you just fresh from China without
Without any common law education and you want to sit that exam, no. But if you come from Hong Kong, yes, you can. From Hong Kong, you a law school and you want to sit the New York exam, yes, you can because it's a common law jurisdiction. So for New York, is only that one year education that counts.
otherwise，everybody goes through the the examination，but then there's no training，two year training，there's no PCCL，that kind of stuff。
係啊，議員，其實 just to do fairness to the requirement of these courses，因為我我我唔 aware， and I also support。
to require those courses because especially conveyancing and basic law, constitutional law are totally different and.
Like like you say in New York, New York bar or California bar, actually you take a master course there, then you can take the exam. But in Hong Kong, the students really have to complete four years undergrad. If we we don't talk about JD.
and then one year PCCL in order to be qualified. So we do have very serious and intensive training for the law graduates. So I think it is fair. Otherwise, it will become a shortcut for those who are not qualified to enter our law schools in Hong Kong, and then they just get that.
趨勢。
然後佢哋 come back喺一個非常 easy 路，所以， in fact， I I would like to see standards。 I from my suggestion is we should see standard。 I mean at least if they want to practice in Hong Kong， they should meet our standard。
We agree, and that's what we do.
I think today's discussion is focusing on one issue, which is the commencement date. So, unless there are any more questions relating to commencement date.
Well, this is related, so they are entitled to ask questions.
啊。
I wonder, I see. I'm not sure. Is that right? Are they related? I mean, we're talking about the substance of the exam. Yes, the exam has been approved by Legco. Legco members are entitled, and indeed, it is their duty to ask questions.
I see that there is another member, Mr. Porte. I
Otherwise, if you have no further questions, I intend to draw this meeting to a close. If there are no further issues.
我唔需要任何問題。謝謝。
係真。
今日下個禮拜先。
啊！誒各位議員啊！誒頭先秘書就同我講，佢就話誒，如果今個禮拜五要即刻上呢個內會做報告咧，就可能未做得切，咁可能要到到下個禮拜五咧，我正係代表呢個委員會去做一個報告。咁如果係噉嘅話，可能要延展嗰個審議期係咪啊？
你下個禮拜三冇？
即係下個禮拜三大會，我會去誒誒動議係延展嗰個咩啊嗰個審議期。但係如果誒即係儘量做得唔得，如果唔我哋而家做唔做？
佢冇comment。
即係譬如。
OK。
今日禮拜二。
最遲禮拜四會出到嘅。
O.K.即後邊。
Okay.
咁咁誒，秘書就驚真係未必講得切。咁如果真係盡量做啦嚇，如果做到講得切而可以將個報告咧嗰個草稿可以交畀律師會去審議，噉就如果做得切就禮拜五，我會代表呢個委員會咧係喺內會嗰度做一個報告。如果真係做唔切，我哋先係誒喺禮拜三。
嘅時候，下個禮拜三我動議去一個延展啦。噉就因為而家大會嗰個議程實在係好飄忽，因為我真係唔知道話如果你要提延展，係咪真係做到咧？如果真係做唔到噉，做到㗎啦，大生。嚇，OK，好，就就噉樣啦。如果各位委員冇其他問題或者意見嘅話咧，啊，法律顧問有冇其他？
乜嘢？嚇！咁好多謝今日啊出席嘅誒代表人士啦，嚇！噉就我會係代表呢個委員會做一個報告，嚇！會議結束。